Once you have both of your simulator set up and you've installed Create React Native App,
设置了模拟器并安装了 create-react-native-app 后
the next step we need to do is actually build our app.
下一步是构建我们的应用
So what will do is head over to your terminal,
转到终端
and you can run Create React Native App.
并运行 create-react-native-app
And then the name of your app,
然后输入你的应用名称
we will call our app that we're going to be building, UdaciFitness.
我们将其称为 UdaciFitness
This is very similar to create React app where we have create React app,
这和 create-react-app 很相似
or in this case Create React Native App,
这里是 create-react-native-app
and then need name of our application that we're building.
然后是要构建的应用的名称
Once that is finished, you'll notice that we have some commands here that we can run.
输完后 可以看到一些可以运行的指令
So what I'm going to do is just as it says here,
我要做的是就像这里说的
I'm going to cd into our app and then I'm going to go ahead and open that up.
cd 到我们的应用目录中 然后打开该应用
So we have all of our code right here,
这是我们的所有代码
and just to show you what this looks like.
为了展示代码看起来怎样
Let's go ahead. And using yarn,
输入 yarn
we will run yarn start to start our app.
运行 yarn start 启动我们的应用
And as that's going, let me go ahead and show you what the code looks like.
在此期间 我们看看代码看起来怎样
So you'll notice here that we have our main App.js file.
这是主 App.js 文件
And this, if you're familiar with React which you should be,
如果你熟悉 React 的话
it should look pretty familiar to you,
这部分看起来应该熟悉
we have this View component.
这是视图组件
Inside of here we have a few Text components that we have are text inside of.
里面是一些文本组件 其中包含一些文本
And then, the rest of this is really just configuration stuff.
剩下的这些是配置文件
So now, you'll notice that when our app started,
现在你会发现 当我们的应用启动时
we have a few options here.
我们有几个选项
If we press a, that will go ahead and run our app in the Android device emulator.
如果按下 a 将在 Android 设备模拟器上运行应用
Pressing q, will display the QR code which is just this right here.
按下 q 将显示二维码 也就是这个二维码
So if you have the Expo app on your phone,
如果你的手机上安装了 Expo 应用
you can go ahead and scan this.
你可以扫描该二维码
And as long as your phone is hooked up to the same network as your computer,
只要手机和计算机连接的是同一个网络
you'll see the app running on your local phone.
就会看到应用在手机上运行
We can press r to restart the packager,
按下 r 可以重启 packager
d to toggle development mode, or i,
按下 d 可以切换开发模式
missed this, to open the iOS simulator.
忘记说 i 了 按下 i 可以打开 iOS 模拟器
Let's go ahead and press i,
我们按下 i
it's going to start the iOS simulator.
将启动 iOS 模拟器
And now on my desktop,
现在在我的桌面上
you'll notice that we have this iOS simulator here with our text right here.
你将看到这个 iOS 模拟器和这段文本
What's cool about this if I go and change this text,
比较酷的是如果我更改这段文本
let's just say, opening up.
例如改成 opening up
You'll notice that we get live reloading here.
你会发现这里在实时重新加载
Then now, I also want to run this on my Android simulator right here, using Genymotion.
现在我想在 Genymotion Android 模拟器上运行此应用
So inside the terminal I will hit a.
在终端里 按下 a
And now we have the code running on our Android emulator over here as well.
现在代码也在 Android 模拟器上运行了